thatweb.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy - ThatWeb.com

At ThatWeb, we are keenly aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we are sharing with you what information we collect when you use our website analysis tool, why we collect it and how we use it to improve your experience. This statement describes the data practices that you consent to by using the ThatWeb web serviceBy using the ThatWeb web service, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Information Collection

All data collected by the ThatWeb tool can be manually accessed by several other means publicly available online (Whois Lookup, Google PageRank, Google Cached Pages, etc.). That is why all reports generated on www.thatweb.com are considered 'public.' As such, they are stored in our database and can alsoevery single report generated on www.thatweb.com is considered 'public' and is thus stored in our database. Furthermore, it can be indexed by search engines.

ThatWeb collects and uses website information to operate its website analysis tool and deliver the services you have requested. This information can include: IP address, domain names, estimated visitors, in-site and off-site SEO analysis, usability, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by ThatWeb for the operation of its service and to provide general statistics regarding use of the ThatWeb web service.

## Use of Personal Information

If you subscribe to our emails ThatWeb may use your personally identifiable email address to inform you of other products or services available from ThatWeb and its affiliates. ThatWeb may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

ThatWeb does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists or your email address to third parties. ThatWeb may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. ThatWeb may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, ThatWeb may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to ThatWeb, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

ThatWeb will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on ThatWeb or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of ThatWeb (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of ThatWeb, or the public.

## Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. However, ThatWeb makes significant efforts to maximize the security of your information. ThatWeb secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

## Cookies

As is the case with almost all advertising-supported websites, ThatWeb uses browser cookie technology. A browser cookie is a small piece of data stored by a web server on your computer, to be read when you reconnect to that web server. ThatWeb includes third-party services which set and read browser cookies. Each third-party company has its own privacy policy.

## Google AdSense

ThatWeb uses Google AdSense, a third-party advertising service operated by Google Inc., to serve ads when you visit ThatWeb. Google AdSense may use “[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)” technology to track information about your visits to ThatWeb and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that Google AdSense determines might be of interest to you. Google AdSense does not track your name, address, email address, or telephone number. If you would like more information about this practice, and to know your choices about not having this information used in this way, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Google Analytics

ThatWeb uses Google Analytics, a third-party website analysis service operated by Google Inc., to collect and report detailed statistics about visits to ThatWeb. When you visit ThatWeb, Google Analytics servers automatically record and collect Log Data sent by your browser, including your computer’s IP address and the referring HTTP location. Google Analytics’ reporting is private. Google Analytics may place or read cookies. If you would like more information about cookies for Google Analytics, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) and scroll to “How does Google use cookies for Google Analytics?”

## Changes to this Statement

ThatWeb will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. ThatWeb encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how ThatWeb is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date below. If material changes should ever be made to policies affecting the sharing of your private information, you will be notified if possible by any email address you have provided and given a chance to opt out before such changes take effect.

Last Updated: 21.10.13
